asiainvestmentservices.biz 2018-09-05

# Privacy Policy | Asia Business Investments and Financing

This Privacy Policy describes ‘Asia Investment Services’ our Contacts, and our specific Investment Services policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of information. When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by the contact form at [Contact Us](https://asiainvestmentservices.biz/contact/)

 **Information Collected Upon submitting your Personal and Business Data to the Website**

When you submit your data, you provide us with personal information, such as your name, gender, address, mobile number, photograph and email address. This information will only be used in terms of skill matching with vacancy review at Asia Investment Services.

 **Protection of Personal and Business Information**

Asia Investment Services takes precautions – including administrative, technical, and physical measures – to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destructionhas implemented and follows industry standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception or processing of Personal Information. We also protect account information by placing it on a secure portion of our web site that is only accessible by certain qualified employees of Consultdustry. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your Personal Information, but are unable to full ensure or warranty the security of any such Personal Information.

 **Third-Party Sites and Services**

Asia Investment Services will not knowingly share your personal information with any third-party sites and services. To make sure your personal information is secure; we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to our employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

 **Legal Disclaimer**

We may disclose your Personal and Business Information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Asia Investment Services. As such, we cannot ensure that your Personal Information will not be disclosed to third parties. For example, we may be legally obligated to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may circumvent our security measures to unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.
